My problem is that a lot of people respond emotionally
when things don't happen as opposed to factually
as to how things get done.
That's probably what drives me crazy the most.
But you also know that that's by design, right?
Like, it's by design that folks are kept ignorant.
It's by design that folks are kept feeling like
the politics and government of it all exists in ivory tower.
You know, there's just this effort that has been made
to create apathy, to, you know, really distract folks
from even feeling like they have any level of power.
And so that's what I love about what you do.
I love about what you do is that you really make it
people's responsibility that they need to get it together,
they need to get the knowledge,
and they need to start just throwing things around
that they don't know about.
And that's what this political comedy documentary is about.
It's about trying to use humor and use comedy
to get folks engaged.
You know, to get folks at least even curious.
I mean, Roland, we are in the age of idiocy.
Oh, yeah.
We are in an era where being ignorant is,
and people will stand on that and look at you crazy
for even seeking knowledge.
So that's what this is about.
I apologize for the simons.
It's a very New York evening.
I got you.
Well, the thing is, again, so when it comes to the documentary
and then, you know, you see you're coming to D.C.
and you're talking to the very people.
See, that's the thing that is important.
I think we do have to, I've been saying this,
that we got to have Schoolhouse Rock 2.0, 3.0,
because when I hear people talk about how frustrated they are,
things don't get done.
And then when I ask them stuff, and then I go,
you do know that's the school board's job.
Then they go, hold up.
They don't.
I'm like, that's not Congress.
Roland, we got to start from scratch.
Yeah.
You understand what I'm saying?
We got to start from scratch.
Like, you already stated that you learned from scratch.
You started when you was seven and eight
by having this juxtaposition to this information.
It's the same way that, like, you got to have books
in babies' rooms even before they can read them.
Yep.
Because it needs to be commonplace that knowledge is around you,
right?
We don't have that civic part of our culture anymore.
And so many of our ancestors, and even just,
not even ancestors, our great grandparents,
our grandparents worked for that.
They fought for that.
They died for that.
And so what we somehow, not somehow,
through great effort, we have been disconnected from that.
And so we got to reconnect to that.
And those of us who see it, it is our responsibility to be it.
And so that's, you know, that's why I made this.
And I made it with my own money.
I mean, that's, you know, I love what you do
because you was like, man, bump y'all.
I'm going to just do this.
And so that is how, but that's how it gets done.
Because if you have to rely on the other sources,
it's going to get dismantled, it's going to get muddled,
it's going to get, you know, just dissolved into BS.
And so anybody who knows my work, that's what I'm about.
So where-